Hubbell Trading Post records, 1882-1968 (bulk 1905-1950)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Sub-group III: Business Books and Records, 1882-1967
  - Series I: Daily Records, 1882-1967
    - Ganado: pawn. 1905-1909 (Volume 350)
    - Ganado: daily sheets. November 19, 1910-November 23, 1911 (Volume 351)
    - Ganado: daybook (p.8-147), miscellaneous. September 19, 1913-October 23, 1915 (Box 352, Folder 1)
    - Ganado: daybook (p.1-43), memo list, groups of checks (p.44-67). 1916-1918 (Box 352, Folder 2)
    - Ganado: daybook (p.273-274), shipments (p.11-175), sheep (p.1-6, 9-10). 1909-1912 (Box 352, Folder 3)
    - Ganado: shipments. September 7, 1912-October 7, 1913 (Box 352, Folder 4)
    - Ganado: shipments (hides, wool, pinons). January 1, 1913-February 13, 1929 (Volume 353)
    - Ganado: shipments. October 12, 1913-July 2, 1914 (Box 354, Folder 1)
    - Ganado: shipments. July 2, 1914-January 2, 1915 (Box 354, Folder 2)
    - Ganado: shipments. February 19, 1916-April 27, 1917 (Box 354, Folder 3)
    - Ganado: shipments. March 11, 1917-August 23, 1922 (Box 354, Folder 4)
    - Ganado: daybook-journal (p.52-125) cover (Mail-Route/Ganado/1918), accounts, mail route teams (p.200-126), miscellaneous. 1918-1927 (Box 354, Folder 5)
    - Ganado: daybook (p.6-252), Indian accounts (p.300-260), shipments (p.1-5). 1915-1921 (Volume 355)
    - Ganado: journal. November 30, 1910-January 31, 1912 (Volume 356)
    - Ganado: journal. February 1, 1912-December 31, 1912 (Volume 357)
    - Ganado: journal. January 1, 1913-December 31, 1913 (Volume 358)
    - Ganado: journal. January 1, 1914-April 27, 1915 (Volume 359)
    - Ganado: journal. April 28, 1915-January 31, 1917 (Volume 360)
    - Ganado: journal. February 1, 1917-June 30, 1919 (Volume 361)
    - Ganado: journal. July 5, 1919-December 31, 1925 (Volume 362)
    - Ganado: accounts. 1911-1912 (Volume 363)
    - Ganado: accounts. 1912 (Volume 364)
    - Ganado: index to previous volume. 1912 (Volume 365)
    - Ganado: accounts. 1913 (Volume 366)
    - Ganado: index to previous volume. 1913 (Volume 367)
    - Ganado: accounts, ledger sheets. 1914-1921 (Volume 368)
    - Ganado: accounts, ledger sheets (parts 1-5). 1914-1924 (Box 369, Folder 1-5)
    - Ganado: accounts, ledgers sheets (parts 6-8). 1914-1925 (Box 370, Folder 1-3)
    - Ganado: accounts, ledgers sheets. 1914-1929 (Box 370, Folder 4)
    - Ganado: accounts, ledgers sheets (parts 1-2). 1926-1930 (Box 370, Folder 5-6)
    - Ganado: cashbook. February 1-December 31, 1912 (Volume 371)
    - Ganado: cashbook. January 1-December 31, 1913 (Volume 372)
    - Ganado: cashbook. September 1, 1913-September 28, 1914 (Volume 373)
    - Ganado: cashbook. January 1, 1914-March 20, 1915 (Volume 374)
    - Ganado: cashbook. September 29, 1914-February 29, 1916 (Volume 375)
    - Ganado: cashbook. March 22, 1915-November 16, 1916 (Volume 376)
    - Ganado: cashbook. March 1, 1916-July 31, 1918 (Volume 377)
    - Ganado: cashbook. November 17, 1916-June 30, 1919 (Volume 378)
    - Ganado: cashbook. July 1, 1919-January 24, 1931 (Volume 379)
    - Ganado: cashbook. August 1, 1918-May 27, 1925 (Volume 380)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts, cattle purchased, wagons from Colorado Moline Plow Co.. 1911-1913 (Volume 381)
    - Ganado: Indian and miscellaneous accounts. 1913-1916 (Volume 382)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts, ledger sheets.. 1913-1930 (Volume 383)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts, ledger sheets (parts 1-5). 1913-1923 (Box 384, Folder 1-5)
    - Ganado: daybook (cover label, "Accounts of Indians working at the Dam"). August 13, 1914-December 14, 1915 (Volume 385)
    - Ganado: Indian and various accounts. 1917-1918 (Volume 386)
    - Ganado: daybook (p.3-105), pawn (p.124-311), orders (p.394-312) 1908-1911 (Volume 387)
    - Ganado: pawn (p.3-53), various orders. April-December 1911, April 1924 (Volume 388)
    - Ganado: pawn. January 1912-September 1924 (Volume 389)
    - Ganado: sheep, goats, cattle, cash. 1912-1935 (Box 390, Folder 1)
    - Ganado: monthly recapitulations. December 1912-June 1923 (Box 390, Folder 2)
    - Ganado: daybook. August 1, 1921-July 11, 1924 (Box 390, Folder 3)
    - Ganado: daybook. July 14, 1924-June 24, 1925 (Box 390, Folder 4)
    - Ganado: daybook. March 1, 1926-September 3, 1928 (Box 390, Folder 5)
    - Ganado: daybook (p.19-23, 26), cash (p.1-12, 14-18), cattle (p.1, 13. 24-25). 1917-1929 (Box 390, Folder 6)
    - Ganado: daybook (p.1-266), rugs (p.280-298), cattle (p.299-). 1929-1933 (Box 391, Folder 1)
    - Ganado: daybook, miscellaneous, pawn. 1933-1938 (Box 391, Folder 2)
    - Ganado: cash account (First National Bank), pawn (p.63-69), sales (p.200, 207-212), cattle (p. 214-215, 220-223), sheep (p. 82-109,70-71, 230-239). 1921-1926 (Box 391, Folder 3)
    - Ganado: Indian and various accounts. 1897-1917 (Box 391, Folder 4)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts, cattle (p.84-87). 1929 (Box 391, Folder 5)
    - Ganado: accounts, ledger sheets (parts 1-5). 1914-1925 (Box 392, Folder 1-5)
    - Ganado: accounts, ledger sheets (parts 6-10). 1914-1925 (Box 393, Folder 1-5)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts, miscellaneous. 1921-1924 (Volume 394)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts (p.13-291, 296-299), sheep (p.282-287, 290-291), miscellaneous. 1924-1927 (Volume 395)
    - Ganado: journal. January 1, 1926-November 30, 1930 (Volume 396)
    - Ganado: rugs (p.35-68), wool (p.69-71, 73), Indian Accounts. 1938-1939 (Volume 397)
    - Ganado: daybook-journal, cash receipts & distribution, purchase journal, sales journal. 1930-1932 (Volume 398)
    - Ganado: daily sheets. January 28-May 19, 1931 (Box 399, Folder 1)
    - Ganado: daily cash sheets. June 14-December 4, 1933 (Box 399, Folder 2)
    - Ganado: daily cash sheets, with monthly recapitulations. June 1, 1934-January 29, 1935 (Box 399, Folder 3)
    - Ganado: daily cash sheets, with monthly recapitulations. February 1-November 30, 1935 (Box 399, Folder 4)
    - Ganado: journal sheets. December 1, 1935-March 9, 1936 (Box 399, Folder 5)
    - Ganado: daily sheets. August 1, 1939-March 23, 1940 (Box 399, Folder 6)
    - Ganado: various accounts, ledger sheets (parts 1-5). 1930-1943 (Box 400, Folder 1-5)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts, ledger sheets (part 1, A-G). 1930-1935 (Box 401, Folder 1)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts, ledger sheets (part 2, H-M). 1930-1935 (Box 401, Folder 2)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts, ledger sheets (part 3, N-Z). 1930-1935 (Box 401, Folder 3)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts. 1938 (Box 401, Folder 4)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts. 1934-1935 (Box 402, Folder 1)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts (various notes on accounts). 1935-1940 (Box 402, Folder 2a)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts (various notes on accounts). 1935-1940 (Box 402, Folder 2b)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts. 1934 (Box 402, Folder 3)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts. 1936-1937 (Box 402, Folder 4)
    - Ganado: farm account, "bread from Bakerite." 1939-1940 (Box 403, Folder 1)
    - Ganado: cashbook. 1942-1944 (Box 403, Folder 2)
    - Ganado: pawn, broken down as to type. 1934-1942 (Box 403, Folder 3)
    - Ganado: rugs, purchases, sales, inventories. 1939-1954 (Box 403, Folder 4)
    - Ganado: rugs, inventories. December 31, 1934, 1954-1964 (Box 403, Folder 5)
    - Ganado: pawn (inventory p.3-19, 20-87, 88-89, 100-247), cash (p.596-594), "Dip a/c (p.593)." 1931-1939 (Volume 404)
    - Ganado: cashbook. December 26, 1942-December 31, 1943 (Volume 405)
    - Ganado: pawn, broken down as to type. 1922-1937 (Volume 406)
    - Ganado: daily sheets (part 1). September 2, 1940-April 30, 1941 (Box 407, Folder 1)
    - Ganado: daily sheets (part 2). May 1-November 29, 1941 (Box 407, Folder 2)
    - Ganado: cashbook. November 30, 1946-December 2, 1950 (Box 407, Folder 3a)
    - Ganado: cashbook. November 30, 1946-December 2, 1950 (Box 407, Folder 3b)
    - Ganado: cashbook. December 4, 1950-August 2, 1952 (Box 407, Folder 4)
    - Ganado: daybook-journal sheets. December 2, 1940-November 30, 1943 (Volume 408)
    - Ganado: daybook-journal sheets. December 1, 1943-November 30, 1947 (Volume 409)
    - Ganado: daybook-journal sheets. December 1, 1947-July 24, 1952 (Volume 410)
    - Ganado: daily sheets. September 1, 1952-May 29, 1953 (Volume 411)
    - Ganado: daybook-cash. May 11-Septmber 30, 1954 (Volume 412)
    - Ganado: daybook-cash. October 1, 1954-April 1, 1955 (Volume 413)
    - Ganado: daybook-cash. April 2-November 10, 1955 (Volume 414)
    - Ganado: daybook-cash. November 11, 1955-June 6, 1956 (Volume 415)
    - Ganado: daybook-cash. June 7-October 27, 1956 (Volume 416)
    - Ganado: daybook-cash. October 28, 1956-April 4, 1957 (Volume 417)
    - Ganado: daybook-cash. April 5-August 10, 1957 (Volume 418)
    - Ganado: daybook-cash. August 12, 1957-February 28, 1958 (Volume 419)
    - Ganado: daybook-cash. March 1-September 15, 1958 (Volume 420)
    - Ganado: daybook-cash. September 16, 1958-March 5, 1959 (Volume 421)
    - Ganado: daybook-cash. March 6-August 3, 1959 (Volume 422)
    - Ganado: daybook-cash sheets. August 3, 1959-February 15, 1966 (Volume 423)
    - Ganado: daybook-cash sheets. October 2, 1963-February 15, 1966 (Volume 424)
    - Ganado: cash journal sheets. June 1, 1953-May 30, 1955 (Volume 425)
    - Ganado: cash journal sheets. May 27, 1955-November 18, 1958 (Volume 426)
    - Ganado: cash journal sheets. November 15, 1958-November 30, 1961 (Volume 427)
    - Ganado: cash journal sheets. December 1, 1962-November 30, 1966 (Volume 428)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts, ledger sheets. 1940-1947 (Volume 429)
    - Ganado: cashbook sheets. October 19, 1951-February 20, 1952 (Box 430, Folder 1)
    - Ganado: cashbook sheets. February 21-June 18, 1952 (Box 430, Folder 2)
    - Ganado: cash accounts. July 21, 1951-February 13, 1953 (Box 430, Folder 3)
    - Ganado: cash accounts. August 1-31, 1953 (Box 430, Folder 4)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts, ledger sheets (parts 1-3). 1951-1957 (Box 430, Folder 5-7)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts, ledger sheets. 1947-1950 (Volume 431)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts, ledger sheets. 1951-1957 (Box 432, Folder 1)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts, ledger sheets. 1952 (Box 432, Folder 2)
    - Ganado: sales, gas. 1940 (Box 432, Folder 3)
    - Ganado: various accounts, ledger sheets. 1943-1945 (Box 432, Folder 4)
    - Ganado: various accounts, ledger sheets. 1948-1949 (Box 432, Folder 5)
    - Ganado: various accounts, ledger sheets. 1949-1959 (Box 432, Folder 6)
    - Ganado: cash. August 1, 1946-August 30, 1957 (Box 432, Folder 7)
    - Ganado: cash. August 23, 1958-June 5, 1959 (Box 432, Folder 8)
    - Ganado: cash (p.211-284). June 6, 1959-June 10, 1960 (Box 432, Folder 9a)
    - Ganado: pawn (p.17-209). March 30, 1949-December 1, 1955 (Box 432, Folder 9b)
    - Ganado: various accounts, ledger sheets (parts 1-3). 1952-1964 (Box 433, Folder 1-3)
    - Ganado: cash (p.70-151). June 11, 1960-April 20, 1961 (Box 433, Folder 4)
    - Ganado: cash. April 21, 1961-March 2, 1962 (Box 433, Folder 5)
    - Ganado: cash (p.40-100). March 3-December 26, 1962 (Box 433, Folder 6)
    - Ganado: cash. December 29, 1962-April 24, 1963 (Box 433, Folder 7)
    - Ganado: cash (p.53-136). March 6, 1964-March 31, 1966 (Box 433, Folder 8)
    - Ganado: cash (p.34-72). April 1, 1966-February 11, 1967 (Box 434, Folder 1)
    - Ganado: pawn (p.186-187). 1942 (Box 434, Folder 2)
    - Ganado: pawn. April 6, 1946-may 4, 1953 (Box 434, Folder 3)
    - Ganado: pawn (p.116-143). June 15, 1957-January 19, 1959 (Box 434, Folder 4a)
    - Ganado: pawn (inventories). 1955-1958 (Box 434, Folder 4b)
    - Ganado: pawn sheets. 1956 (Box 434, Folder 5)
    - Ganado: pawn (inventories). 1959-1964 (Box 434, Folder 6)
    - Ganado: pawn (inventories). 1964-1965 (Box 434, Folder 7)
    - Ganado: sheep, notations on wool weights (p.100-102, 106-107). 1954-1955 (Box 434, Folder 8a)
    - Ganado: sheep, notations on wool weights (p.100-102, 106-107). 1954-1955 (Box 434, Folder 8b)
    - Ganado: sheep (p.82-97). 1956-1959 (Box 435, Folder 1a-1b)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts, index to book only, book to which this is the index has not been found. (Box 435, Folder 2)
    - Ganado: Indian accounts, index to pages only, book from which these pages were removed has not been found. (Box 435, Folder 3)
    - Greasewood: Indian and various accounts. 1930-1931 (Box 435, Folder 4)
    - Greasewood: sheep. 1930-1932 (Box 435, Folder 5)
    - Greasewood: daily and monthly sheets (part 1). January 1-November 30, 1931 (Box 435, Folder 6)
    - Greasewood: daily and monthly sheets (part 2). December 1, 1931-June 30, 1932 (Box 435, Folder 7)
    - Greasewood: daily and monthly sheets (part 3). July 1-December 31, 1932 (Box 435, Folder 8)
    - Greasewood: daily and monthly sheets (part 4). January 1-July 17, 1931 (Box 435, Folder 9)
    - Greasewood: Indian accounts. 1931 (Box 436, Folder 1)
    - Greasewood: Indian and various accounts. 1931-1933 (Box 436, Folder 2)
    - Greasewood: Indian accounts. 1931-1933 (Box 436, Folder 3)
    - Greasewood: Indian and various accounts (p.49-116), shipments of rugs, wool, other, pawn (p.197-190), "cash due on wool (p.45)." 1930-1933 (Box 436, Folder 4)
    - Greasewood: Indian and various accounts. 1933 (Box 436, Folder 5)
    - Greasewood: Indian and various accounts. 1933 (Box 436, Folder 6)
    - Greasewood: Indian accounts. 1933 (Box 436, Folder 7)
    - Greasewood: Indian and various accounts, pawn. 1933-1934 (Box 436, Folder 8)
    - Greasewood: Indian and various accounts. 1933-1935 (Box 436, Folder 9)
    - Greasewood: sales, cash, and merchandise, "Business at Navajo Trading Post," rugs, list of government checks. 1933 (Box 436, Folder 10)
    - Greasewood: sales, cash, and merchandise (p.34-39), shipments received (p.95-96),. 1933-1935 (Box 436, Folder 11)
    - Greasewood: sales, cash (p.75-81), government checks and payroll (p.1-41). 1933-1935 (Box 437, Folder 1)
    - Greasewood: cash, sheep, skins, dipping records, miscellaneous records. 1933 (Box 437, Folder 2)
    - Greasewood: various accounts. 1933-1935 (Box 437, Folder 3)
    - Greasewood: various accounts. 1933-1935 (Box 437, Folder 4)
    - Greasewood: Indian and various accounts. 1933-1936 (Box 437, Folder 5)
    - Greasewood: shipments sent and received, "list of Navajo rugs bot." 1933-1934 (Box 437, Folder 6)
    - Greasewood: sheep (p.1-18), "goat reduction (p.21-33)," government sheep act (p.100-150), sheep expense (p.200), Indian accounts (p.200), pawn (p.44-49). 1932-1934 (Box 437, Folder 7a-7b)
    - Greasewood: sheep. 1933 (Box 437, Folder 8)
    - Greasewood: rugs (bought, inventory, p.1-24, 29-48), skins (p.25-28), wool and mohair (p.50-51, 80-83). 1934-1935 (Box 437, Folder 9)
    - Greasewood: accounts (C.E. Rubi, F.M. Parker), Indian accounts. 1934-1935 (Box 437, Folder 10)
    - Greasewood: daily sheets with monthly summary for 1935 (part 1). February 22-July 31, 1935 (Box 438, Folder 1)
    - Greasewood: daily sheets with monthly summary for 1935 (part 2). August 1-December 31, 1935 (Box 438, Folder 2)
    - Greasewood: daily sheets with monthly summary for 1935 (part 3). January 1-July 15, 1936 (Box 438, Folder 3)
    - Greasewood: bi-weekly summary. August 1-15, 1936 (Box 438, Folder 4)
    - Hollywood: cash journal/general journal, cash receipts, cash (check) and distribution, accounts. 1926-1928 (Box 438, Folder 5)
    - Hub Store: various accounts. 1934-1938 (Box 438, Folder 6)
    - Lorenzo Hubbell Motor Company: car sales. 1947-1949 (Box 439, Folder 1)
    - Lorenzo Hubbell Motor Company: car sales. 1949-1952 (Box 439, Folder 2a-2b)
    - Lorenzo Hubbell Motor Company: daily summary of labor and material sales. August 30-June 19, 1952 (Box 439, Folder 3)
    - Keams Canyon: sheep, goats, cattle. 1912-1915 (Box 439, Folder 4a-4b)
    - Keams Canyon: various accounts (part 1). 1914-1916 (Box 439, Folder 5a)
    - Keams Canyon: various accounts (enclosure, "Old a/c's in"). 1914-1916 (Box 439, Folder 5b)
    - Keams Canyon: various accounts (part 2). 1914-1916 (Box 439, Folder 6)
    - Keams Canyon: various accounts. 1914-1917 (Box 439, Folder 7)
    - Marble Canyon: cash sales and "paid outs." November 1946-August 1948 (Box 440, Folder 1)
    - Marble Canyon: receipts and disbursements. November 1951-January 1952 (Box 440, Folder 2)
    - Nakai Tso: cash journal, with yearly summary sheets. December 1, 1938-November 30, 1939 (Box 440, Folder 3)
    - Nakai Tso: daily and monthly sheets, with yearly summary (part 1). January 1-June 30, 1941 (Box 440, Folder 4)
    - Nakai Tso: daily and monthly sheets, with yearly summary (part 2). July 1-December 31, 1941 (Box 440, Folder 5)
    - Nakai Tso: daily and monthly sheets, with yearly summary (part 3). January 1-June 30, 1942 (Box 440, Folder 6)
    - Nakai Tso: daily and monthly sheets, with yearly summary (part 4). July 1-November 30, 1942 (Box 440, Folder 7)
    - Nakai Tso: Indian accounts. 1946-1947 (Box 440, Folder 8)
    - Oraibi: daily sheets (part 1). July 9, 1917-March 30, 1918 (Box 441, Folder 1)
    - Oraibi: daily sheets (part 2). April 1-August 30, 1918 (Box 441, Folder 2)
    - Oraibi: daily sheets (part 3). September 2-December 30, 1918 (Box 441, Folder 3)
    - Oraibi: daily sheets (part 4). January 1-May 30, 1919 (Box 441, Folder 4)
    - Oraibi: daily sheets (part 5). June 2-August 31, 1919 (Box 441, Folder 5)
    - Oraibi: daily sheets (part 6). September 1-December 31, 1919 (Box 441, Folder 6)
    - Oraibi: cash (p.181-185), shipments (sent & received). 1924-1925 (Volume 442)
    - Oraibi: daybook (p.1-12 missing). January 1-October 8, 1923 (Box 443, Folder 1)
    - Oraibi: accounts, ledger sheets. 1921-1928 (Box 443, Folder 2)
    - Oraibi: various accounts, ledger sheets (includes taxes on various properties). 1929-1940 (Box 443, Folder 3)
    - Oraibi: journal. January 1-May 7, 1924 (Box 443, Folder 4)
    - Oraibi: journal. May 8-October 31, 1924 (Box 443, Folder 5a-5b)
    - Oraibi: invoice record, contracts, flour, coffee (p.295-298). 1924-1925 (Box 443, Folder 6)
    - Oraibi: shipments from Winslow. May 12, 1927-September 1, 1928 (Box 443, Folder 7)
    - Oraibi: Indian accounts, ledger sheets. 1921-1927 (Volume 444)
    - Oraibi: Indian accounts, ledger sheets (part 1, A-E). 1927-1930 (Box 445, Folder 1)
    - Oraibi: Indian accounts, ledger sheets (part 2, F-J). 1927-1930 (Box 445, Folder 2)
    - Oraibi: Indian accounts, ledger sheets (part 3, K-R). 1927-1930 (Box 445, Folder 3)
    - Oraibi: Indian accounts, ledger sheets (part 4, S-Z). 1927-1930 (Box 445, Folder 4)
    - Oraibi: shipments from Winslow. 1928-1933 (Box 445, Folder 5)
    - Oraibi: shipments from Winslow. October 17, 1933-December 26, 1934 (Box 445, Folder 6)
    - Oraibi: cattle. 1925 (Box 445, Folder 7)
    - Oraibi: sheep and cattle. September-October 1927 (Box 445, Folder 8)
    - Oraibi: cattle. October 1927 (Box 445, Folder 9)
    - Oraibi: various accounts. 1930 (Volume 446)
    - Oraibi: general journal. January 1-December 31, 1931 (Volume 447)
    - Oraibi. Indian and various accounts. 1931-1939 (Box 448)
    - Oraibi. Indian and various accounts. 1931-1939 (Box 449)
    - Oraibi: daily and monthly sheets (part 1). January 1-June 30, 1932 (Box 450, Folder 1)
    - Oraibi: daily and monthly sheets (part 2). July 1-November 30, 1932 (Box 450, Folder 2)
    - Oraibi: daily and monthly sheets (part 3). December 1, 1932-May 31, 1933 (Box 450, Folder 3)
    - Oraibi: daily and monthly sheets (part 4). June 1-November 30, 1933 (Box 450, Folder 4)
    - Oraibi: daily and monthly sheets (part 5). December 1, 1933-June 30, 1934 (Box 450, Folder 5)
    - Oraibi: daily and monthly sheets (part 6). July 2-December 29, 1934 (Box 450, Folder 6)
    - Oraibi: daily and monthly sheets (part 7). January 1-July 31, 1935 (Box 451, Folder 1)
    - Oraibi: daily and monthly sheets (part 8). August 1, 1935-February 29, 1936 (Box 451, Folder 2)
    - Oraibi: daily and monthly sheets (part 9). March 2-September 30, 1936 (Box 451, Folder 3)
    - Oraibi: daily and monthly sheets (part 10). October 1, 1936-April 30, 1937 (Box 451, Folder 4)
    - Oraibi: daily and monthly sheets (part 11). May 1-November 30, 1937 (Box 451, Folder 5)
    - Oraibi: daily and monthly sheets (part 12). December 1, 1937-May 31, 1938 (Box 452, Folder 1)
    - Oraibi: daily and monthly sheets (part 13). June 1-December 31, 1938 (Box 452, Folder 2)
    - Oraibi: daily and monthly sheets (part 14). January 2-June 29, 1939 (Box 452, Folder 3)
    - Oraibi: daily and monthly sheets (part 15). July 1-December 31, 1939 (Box 452, Folder 4)
    - Oraibi: daily and monthly sheets (part 16). January 1-June 29, 1940 (Box 452, Folder 5)
    - Oraibi: daily and monthly sheets (part 17). July 1-November 30, 1940 (Box 453, Folder 1)
    - Oraibi: daily working sheets (part 1). July 31-May 14, 1937 (Box 453, Folder 2)
    - Oraibi: daily working sheets (part 2). May 13-April 12, 1937 (Box 453, Folder 3)
    - Oraibi: cashbook. June 2, 1930-January 10, 1931 (Box 453, Folder 4a-4b)
    - Oraibi: cashbook, journal memo. 1933 (Box 453, Folder 5)
    - Oraibi: cashbook, journal memo. 1934 (Box 453, Folder 6a-6b)
    - Oraibi: cashbook. October 1, 1934-March2, 1935 (Box 453, Folder 7)
    - Oraibi: cashbook. July 1-November 26, 1935 (Box 453, Folder 8)
    - Oraibi: cash accounts, "cash over & shortages." 1934 (Box 454, Folder 1)
    - Oraibi: pawn, wagons (ordered), wagons (sold), miscellaneous. 1934-1935 (Box 454, Folder 2)
    - Oraibi: Indian accounts, dipping records, miscellaneous. 1930 (Box 454, Folder 3)
    - Oraibi: Indian accounts and records ("Sheep no.1"). 1934 (Box 454, Folder 4)
    - Oraibi: Indian accounts and records ("Sheep no.2"). 1935 (Box 454, Folder 5)
    - Oraibi: pawn. November 27, 1939-March 19, 1943 (Box 454, Folder 6)
    - Oraibi: rugs. April 1, 1933-October 1, 1934 (Box 454, Folder 7)
    - Oraibi: rugs. October 25, 1937-August 30, 1938 (Box 454, Folder 8a-8b)
    - Oraibi: wool. 1939 (Box 454, Folder 9)
    - Oraibi: sheep, some cattle. 1932-1933 (Box 454, Folder 10a-10b)
    - Oraibi: dipping records, sheep & goat skins. 1934 (Box 454, Folder 11a-11b)
    - Oraibi: Indian accounts, ledger sheets. 1928-1947 (Box 455)
    - Oraibi: various accounts, ledger sheets. 1932-1943 (Volume 456)
    - Oraibi: various accounts, ledger sheets. 1935-1936 (Volume 457)
    - Oraibi: rugs, jewelry, pottery (shipments, consignments, returns). 1930-1936 (Volume 458)
    - Oraibi: daily sheets with monthly summaries (part 1). January-March 1942 (Box 459, Folder 1)
    - Oraibi: daily sheets with monthly summaries (part 2). April-June 1942 (Box 459, Folder 2)
    - Oraibi: daily sheets with monthly summaries (part 3). July-September 1942 (Box 459, Folder 3)
    - Oraibi: daily sheets with monthly summaries (part 4). October-December 1942 (Box 459, Folder 4)
    - Oraibi: daily sheets with monthly summaries (part 1). January-June 1945 (Box 459, Folder 5)
    - Oraibi: daily sheets with monthly summaries (part 2). July-December 1945 (Box 459, Folder 6)
    - Oraibi: daily and monthly sheets (part 1). December 1946-June 1947 (Box 460, Folder 1)
    - Oraibi: daily and monthly sheets (part 2). July-December 1947 (Box 460, Folder 2)
    - Oraibi: daily and monthly sheets (part 3). January-June 1948 (Box 460, Folder 3)
    - Oraibi: daily and monthly sheets (part 4). July-December 1948 (Box 460, Folder 4)
    - Oraibi: daily sheets. May-June 1952 (Box 460, Folder 5)
    - Oraibi: cashbook. May 6, 1944-January 1, 1946 (Box 460, Folder 6)
    - Oraibi: orders. May 1,1933-January 2, 1935 (Box 460, Folder 7)
    - Oraibi: trail balances, white and Indian accounts. 1933-1934 (Box 461, Folder 1)
    - Oraibi: various accounts, ledger sheets (parts 1-3). 1940-1946 (Box 461, Folder 2-4)
    - Oraibi: rugs. 1943-1946 (Box 461, Folder 5)
    - Oraibi: cattle. (Box 461, Folder 6a-6b)
    - Pinon: cashbook, pawn, shipments. 1916-1922 (Box 462, Folder 1)